

Giorgi Gergedava

FRONT END DEVELOPER

I am writing to express my strong interest in the Experienced Frontend Developer position. With my experience in front end development and my passion for creating exceptional user experiences, I am confident that I would be a valuable asset to your team.

Having worked in the industry, I have honed my skills in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and have a deep understanding of responsive design principles.

https://giorgigergedava.github.io/Portfolio/

SKILLS

- Front-End Programming: HTML5, CSS3, AJAX
- Front End Web Development,
 Javascript
- Web Technologies: AngularJS, jQuery, Bootstrap
- Website Updating
- Responsive design
- Source and Version Control: Git, GitHub
- Figma
- Tilda
- WordpressWebsite Maintenance
- Website Maintenance
- Creativity and Innovation
- Google Analytics
- Marketing
- Critical Thinking
- Strong Work Ethic

LANGUAGE

- Georgian
- English
- Russian

CONTACT



+393508090676



giogergedava123@gmail.com

in

EDUCATION

DAVID AGMASHENEBELI UNIVERSITY

(Business Administration)

2013-2014

SEU GEORGIAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY

(Business Administration and Marketing)

2013-2017

Academy Of Digital Industries

I started studying at the academy this year, where I will take a full course to become a Full Stack developer. I am taking: html, css, JavaScript (node.js Angular.js) react and python courses.

EXPERIENCE

TELETRADE

Licensed Forex Trader with experience in managing forex portfolios and optimizing trading strategies as a manager ,With the help of Meta Trade 4 program.

2014 - 2016

HD FOREX

Licensed Forex Trader with experience in managing forex portfolios and optimizing trading strategies as a manager ,With the help of Meta Trade 4 program.

2016-2019

UP WORK

- Designed and updated layouts to meet usability and performance requirements.
- Researched emerging web technologies and trends for possible incorporation into sites.
- Coded using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.

2023-2024

Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.
 London, United Kingdom (Remote)